# GREG MROWCZYNSKI

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

gregmdev30@gmail.com | +44 07492 204 194 | Coventry, England

www: gregmdev.co.uk | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/greg-mrowczynski | Github: github.com/greg19850

#### SUMMARY

Full Stack coding enthusiast with experience in building web pages and applications. Programmer skilled in writing clean, debugged code in **JavaScript**, **React** and **Python**, with use of **web-APIs** and **SQL databases**. I'm thrilled for the opportunity to develop my technical skills, and contribute to success of future projects I will participate in.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript

■ Python

■ PHP

■ TypeScript (basics)

■ React

■ Flask

■ Vue.js

■ Laravel

■ MySQL

■ PostgreSQL

■ Node.js

■ Express.js

■ HTML / CSS

■ Bootstrap 4 / 5

■ Git

■ Jest

■ Linux / Unix

■ Test Driven Development

■ Agile methodologies

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2023 - Present

## **Junior Software Developer**

TransParagon Global Limited

- Developing dedicated platform for clients, used for supply chain management and products design. Creating and modernising app architecture, with use of JavaScript and React.
- Back end development, integration of data from back end services and database. Using Python and relational databases (PostgreSQL).
- Troubleshooting and fixing bugs.
- Working in team with experienced developers.
- ◆ Face Detection App Detects and marks faces on any uploaded photo, and outputs bounding boxes for all detected faces. Front end using React and Tachyons CSS, back end using Express.js, connecting with PostgreSQL database, and using Sky Biometry face detection API.
- Personal Project: Password checker application connecting with pwned API, and checking password against hundreds of millions of real world passwords previously exposed in data breaches. Built in **Python**.
- ◆ Personal Project: Restaurant Page Full restaurant page, with table booking, menu – with online order option, checkout and payment page (connecting with PayPal), bookings page and admin panel. Built in PHP, MySQL HTML, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Junior Software Developer Northcoders

- Collaborated with team of developers, created SkinScan Full Stack application, which compares user skin photo, with photos from database, and assess probability of skin cancer.
  Application use Vue.js for Ul/front end interface,
  Python(PyTorch & Flask) for results analysis, MySQL database, and is hosted on AWS cloud server.
- Wrote front end and back end applications which connected with SQL databases and RESTful API's.
- Worked in a fast-paced high performance tech team.
- Utilised Agile and Scrum methodologies in everyday work.
- Regular code reviews.
- Developed fully tested applications.

Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

## **Front End Web Developer**

Freelance

- ◆ Planned, designed and developed 2 websites, for individual clients, by applying **JavaScript**, **React**, **HTML**, and **CSS** skills.
- ◆ Remodelled online medical catalogue.
- Communicated with clients through development process, in order to deliver fully satisfying product.
- ◆ Created over 10 personal projects.

Oct 2018- Dec 2022

## **Quality Engineer**

IMK Automotive / LEVC

### **EDUCATION**

### **Masters Degree in Business Administration**

Warsaw School Of Business And Int. Finances